Finding Aid for Alumni Association (University of Michigan) records, 1845-2001
Bentley Historical Library
- Alumnae Council Files, 1921-1998
  - Alumnae Club File, 1931-1956
    - Toledo, Ohio (Box 113)
    - Trenton (Box 113)
    - Twin Cities (Minneapolis-St. Paul), Minnesota (Box 113)
    - Washington, DC (Box 113)
    - Wayne (Box 113)
    - Youngstown, Ohio (Box 113)
  - Alumnae Council, 1967 (Box 157)
  - Alumnae Council Scholarships, Fellowships, and Funds, 1931-1998
    - General Alumni Council and Alumni Club Scholarships, 1992-1994 (Box 157)
    - Fellowship Committee, 1930-1937 (Box 157)
    - Individual Fund/Endowment, 1945-1998
      - Assistance Fund for the Continuing Education of Women, 1967-1974 (Box 157)
      - Benson, Gertrude, 1992 (Box 157)
      - Brown, Frances J., 1971-1982 (Box 157)
      - Buzby, Elizabeth M., 1975-1976 (Box 157)
      - Conger, Julia Henning, 1964-1965 (Box 157)
      - Conger, Lucille Bailey, 1971 (Box 157)
      - Demaline, Sue Ann Vogt, 1998 (Box 157)
      - Elliott, Lucy, 1931-1960 (Box 157)
      - Emanuel, Julia, 1965-1973 (Box 157)
      - England, H. Catherine, 1976-1991 (Box 157)
      - Fairman, Louise, 1949-1972 (Box 157)
      - Gay, Lorraine, 1973-1974 (Box 157)
      - Hartwig, Marie, 1983 (Box 157)
      - Hinsdale, Mary Louise, 1946-1962 (Box 157)
      - Host, Margaret Ayers, 1976-1987 (Box 157)
      - Kellogg, Catherine Neafie Professorship, 1949-1954 (Box 157)
      - Lawler, Abigail Marie Shaw Lawler, 1993 (Box 157)
      - McCrery Fund, 1998 (Box 157)
      - Mueller, Annie Belger, 1979 (Box 157)
      - Myers, Alison Tennant Myers, 1971-1972 (Box 157)
      - Palmer, Alice Freeman, Professorship, 1960-1969 (Box 157)
      - Sanders, Claire M, 1954-1964 (Box 157)
      - Seeley, Laurel Harper, 1945-1957 (Box 157)
      - Van den Bosch, Elizabeth, 1971-1987 (Box 157)
      - Welker, Bertha, 1966-1976 (Box 157)
      - Willison, Mable C., 1962-1968 (Box 157)
      - Miscellaneous, 1955-1972 (Box 157)
    - Manuals, 1965-1970
      - In-State Scholarship Manual, 1970 (Box 157)
      - Out-of-State Scholarship Manual, 1965 (Box 157)
      - Scholarship Manual, 1965 (Box 157)
    - Michigan Giving Fund, 1955-1978 (Box 157)
      (formerly Alumni Fund; see also Michigan Annual Giving Scholars)
    - Scholarship Recipients, 1952-1975 (Box 157)
    - Scholarship Selection Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 157)
    - Scholarships and Fellowships (historical), 1931-1988 (Box 157)
  - Committee Files, Circa 1931-1975; undated
    (includes special events)
    - Alumnae Luncheon, 1959 (Box 132)
    - Alumnae Secretary's reports, 1959-1961 (Box 132)
    - Alumni Leadership Conference, 1972 (Box 132)
    - Alumni Living Unit Pilot Committee, 1961 (Box 132)
    - Ann Arbor Day, 1961-1963 (Box 132)
    - Bookplates (Box 132)
    - Long Range Planning Committee, 1966-1967 (Box 132)
    - Mary Markley House reunion, 1975; 2 folders (Box 132)
    - Membership Committee, 1957-1968 (Box 132)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 132)
    - Music School Alumni Association concerts, 1973-1974 (Box 132)
    - Nominating Committee, 1961-1969 (Box 132)
    - Program Committee, 1958-1968 (Box 132)
    - Publicity Committee, 1960-1968; 2 folders (Box 132)
    - Scholarship Committee (in-state and out-of-state), Circa 1931-1970
      - Club Scholarships, 1962-1964 (Box 132)
      - General, 1956-1970; 4 folders (Box 132)
      - Honors Program, 1964-1965 (Box 132)
      - Jackson student project (Box 132)
      - Manual, circa 1963-1964; 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 132)
      - Recipients, 1931-1949; 1960-1970; 4 folders (Box 132)
  - Correspondence and Miscellaneous Files, 1931-1967
    - 1931-1946 (Box 114)
      (including World War II letters)
    - 1931-1946 (Box 115)
      (including World War II letters, continued)
    - 1947-1957 (Box 116)
    - 1947-1957 (Box 117)
    - Center for Continuing Education of Women, 1963-1967 (Box 117)
    - Henderson House file, 1938-1957 (Box 117)
  - Local Club Files
    - Milwaukee (Box 133)
    - New York (Box 133)
    - Syracuse (Box 133)
    - Washington D.C. (Box 133)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 133)
    - Miscellaneous club rosters, 1960-1968; 3 folders (Box 133)
  - Marjorie Williams Papers, 1959-1962
    (1985 accession)
    - Alice Freeman Palmer Professor (AFPP) Committee Reports, 1958-1962 (Box 133)
    - Alumnae Clubs, 1960-1961 (Box 133)
    - Alumni Association Meetings, 1959-1961 (Box 133)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1962 (Box 133)
    - Development Council Reports, 1961 (Box 133)
    - Field Secretaries Bulletin, 1959-1961 (Box 133)
    - Governing Board Meetings (bulk, 1960), 1958-1962 (Box 133)
    - Henderson House Meetings, 1959-1962 (Box 133)
    - Membership, 1959-1962 (Box 133)
    - Michigan Constitutional Convention, 1960-1961 (Box 133)
    - Newsletters, 1959-1961 (Box 133)
    - Nominating Committee Reports, 1959-1962 (Box 133)
    - Operation Friendship Meetings, 1958-1962 (Box 133)
    - President's Workshops Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 133)
    - Program Committee Meeting Minutes, 1960-1961 (Box 133)
    - Publicity Committee Meeting Minutes, 1960 (Box 133)
    - Scholarship Committee Meetings, 1960-1962 (Box 133)
    - Service Citation Committee Reports, 1959-1961 (Box 133)
    - Student Governors Meetings, 1959-1962 (Box 133)
    - Ways and Means Committee Meetings, 1959-1962 (Box 133)
  - Michigan League Building Fund Campaign File, 1921-1926
    - 1921-1926 (Box 105)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 106)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 107)
    - 1921-1926 (Box 108)
  - Minutes and Governing Board Papers, 1954-1974
    - Minutes, 1962-1974; 2 folders (Box 131)
    - Governing Board papers, 1954-1965; 2 folders (Box 132)
  - Responses to Alumnae Council Questionnaires, 1924
    (see separately bound index)
    - A-Am, 1924 (Box 109)
    - An-Ay, 1924 (Box 109)
    - B-Bak, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Bal-Barn, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Barr-Bee, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Beg-Bet, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Bev-Blair, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Blake-Bos, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Bot-Bre, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Bri-Brownell, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Browning-Butler, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Butter-Cars, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Cart-Chap, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Char-Cla, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Cle-Cone, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Cong-Corb, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Croc-Crosby, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Cross-Davies, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Davis-Den, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Dep-Dou, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Dow-Dys, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Ea-Eng, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Eni-Fin, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Fis-Fox, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Fr-Gib, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Gid-Good, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Gor-Grip, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Gris-Hall, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Hals-Harr, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Hart-Haz, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Hea-Her, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Hes-Hob, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Hoc-Howard, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Howe-Hum, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Hun-Jac, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Jae-Joh, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Jon-Kee, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Kei-Kim, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Kin-Knir, 1924 (Box 109)
    - Knis-Kyes, 1924 (Box 109)
    - La-Len, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Leo-Lit, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Liv-Ly, 1924 (Box 110)
    - M-McD, 1924 (Box 110)
    - McE-McL, 1924 (Box 110)
    - McM-Man, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Mar-Maz, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Me-Miller, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Milligan-Morr, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Mors-Neu, 1924 (Box 110)
    - New-Ny, 1924 (Box 110)
    - O-Paris, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Park-Ped, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Peele-Pope, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Poppy-Q, 1924 (Box 110)
    - R-Re, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Rh-Robi, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Robs-Ry, 1924 (Box 110)
    - S-Schr, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Schu-Se, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Sh-Sl, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Sm-Sn, 1924 (Box 110)
    - So-Step, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Stev-Sto, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Str-Sy, 1924 (Box 110)
    - T-Ti, 1924 (Box 110)
    - To-Ty, 1924 (Box 110)
    - U-V, 1924 (Box 110)
    - W-Was, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Wat-Wellman, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Wells-Wid, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Wie-Will, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Wilm-Woo, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Wood-Wy, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Y-Z, 1924 (Box 110)
    - Miscellaneous, 1924 (Box 110)
- Alumni Club Files, Circa 1923-1957; 1991-1997 (with gaps); undated
  The Alumni Club Files (Boxes 68-96; and 168) and Alumnae Club Files (Boxes 111-113) series covers the years 1923-1997. The records are arranged alphabetically by the name of the cities or countries in which alumni/alumnae clubs were in operation. Material in these files pertains to the development and organizations of these clubs and gives evidence of the programming undertaken by the clubs and their relations with the overall Alumni Association. Correspondence with alumni/alumnae in the various cities is included in these files although much of it is routine in nature. Researchers interested alumni activities in a particular location should note that information on that location may overlap between the two different sequences (i.e., Akron, Ohio in Box 68 and Box 111). Each range of club files are broken down into two parts. The (Pt.1 ) files is located offsite in boxes 68-96, the (Pt. 2) files are located in box 168-as they were processed at a later date.
  - A-D (Pt. 1)
    - Adrian (Box 68)
    - Akron, Ohio (Box 68)
    - Albany, New York (Box 68)
    - Albion (Box 68)
    - Albuquerque, New Mexico (Box 68)
    - Alcona County (Box 68)
    - Allegan (Box 68)
    - Alma (Box 68)
    - Alpena (Box 68)
    - Ames, Iowa (Box 68)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 68)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 69)
    - Argentina (Box 69)
    - Asheville, North Carolina (Box 69)
    - Ashtabula, Ohio (Box 69)
    - Atlanta, Georgia (Box 69)
    - Auburn, New York (Box 69)
    - Aurora, Illinois (Box 69)
    - Austin, Texas (Box 69)
    - Bad Axe (Box 69)
    - Baltimore, Maryland (Box 69)
    - Baraga County (Box 69)
    - Bartlesville, Oklahoma (Box 69)
    - Basin, Wyoming (Box 69)
    - Battle Creek (Box 69)
    - Bay City (Box 69)
    - Beacon, New York (Box 69)
    - Beloit, Wisconsin (Box 69)
    - Benton Harbor-St. Joseph (Box 69)
    - Beulah (Box 69)
    - Big Rapids (Box 70)
    - Billings, Montana (Box 70)
    - Binghampton, New York (Box 70)
    - Birmingham, Alabama (Box 70)
    - Birmingham, Michigan (Box 70)
    - Blackhawk County, Iowa (Box 70)
    - Boise, Idaho (Box 70)
    - Bombay, India (Box 70)
    - Boston, Massachusetts (Box 70)
    - Boulder, Colorado (Box 70)
    - Brazil (Box 70)
    - Bridgeport, Connecticut (Box 70)
    - Buchanan (Box 70)
    - Bucyrus (Box 70)
    - Buffalo, New York (Box 71)
    - Butte, Montana (Box 71)
    - Cadillac (Box 71)
    - Calumet (Box 71)
    - Camp Hill, Pennsylvania (Box 71)
    - Camp Lee, Virginia (Box 71)
    - Canal Zone (Box 71)
    - Canandaigua, New York (Box 71)
    - Canton, China (Box 71)
    - Canton, Ohio (Box 71)
    - Caro (Box 71)
    - Casper, Wyoming (Box 71)
    - Cassopolis (Box 71)
    - Cedar Rapids, Iowa (Box 71)
    - Central California (Box 71)
    - Central Florida (Box 71)
    - Central Georgia (Box 71)
    - Central Jersey (Box 71)
    - Charleston, West Virginia (Box 71)
    - Charleston, South Carolina (Box 71)
    - Charlevoix (Box 71)
    - Charlotte, Michigan (Box 71)
    - Charlotte, North Carolina (Box 71)
    - Chattanooga, Tennessee (Box 71)
    - Cheboygan (Box 72)
    - Cheyenne, Wyoming (Box 72)
    - Chicago, Illinois (Box 72)
    - Chicago, Illinois (Box 73)
      (see also box 134 in Photographs: Class Reunion series
    - Chile (Box 73)
    - Chillicothe, Ohio (Box 73)
    - Chungking, China (Box 73)
    - Cincinnati, Ohio (Box 73)
    - Circleville, Ohio (Box 73)
    - Clare (Box 73)
    - Clearfield, Pennsylvania (Box 73)
    - Cleveland, Ohio (Box 73)
    - Clinton County (Box 73)
    - Coldwater (Box 73)
    - Colombia (Box 73)
    - Colorado Springs, Colorado (Box 73)
    - Columbus, Ohio (Box 74)
    - Corning, New York (Box 74)
    - Corpus Christi, Texas (Box 74)
    - Corvallis, Oregon (Box 74)
    - Cuba (Box 74)
    - Dallas, Texas (Box 74)
    - Danville, Illinois (Box 74)
    - Davenport, Iowa (Box 74)
    - Dayton, Ohio (Box 74)
    - Dearborn (Box 74)
    - Denver, Colorado (Box 74)
    - Des Moines, Iowa (Box 74)
    - Des Moines (Box 75)
    - Detroit (Box 75)
    - Detroit (Box 76)
    - Dowagiac (Box 76)
    - Dubuque, Iowa (Box 76)
    - Duluth, Minnesota (Box 76)
    - Dunkirk, New York (Box 76)
  - A-D (Pt. 2)
    - Atlanta (Box 168)
    - Austin (Box 168)
    - Central Florida (Box 168)
    - Central Illinois (Box 168)
    - Cleveland (Box 168)
    - Dallas (Box 168)
    - Denver (Box 168)
  - E-M (Pt. 1)
    - East Chicago, Indiana (Box 77)
    - Ecorse (Box 77)
    - Ecuador (Box 77)
    - Elkhart County, Indiana (Box 77)
    - Elmira (Box 77)
    - El Paso, Texas (Box 77)
    - Erie, Pennsylvania (Box 77)
    - Escanaba (Box 77)
    - Evansville, Indiana (Box 77)
    - Fargo, North Dakota (Box 77)
    - Fenton (Box 77)
    - Ferndale (Box 77)
    - Findlay, Ohio (Box 78)
    - Flint (Box 78)
    - Fort Benning, Georgia (Box 78)
    - Fort Lauderdale, Florida (Box 78)
    - Fort Wayne, Indiana (Box 78)
    - Fort Worth, Texas (Box 78)
    - Fox River Valley, Illinois (Box 78)
    - Frankfort (Box 78)
    - Fremont (Box 78)
    - Galveston, Texas (Box 79)
    - Gary, Indiana (Box 79)
    - Geneva, New York (Box 79)
    - Gogebic Range (Box 79)
    - Grand Haven (Box 79)
    - Grand Ledge (Box 79)
    - Grand Rapids (Box 79)
    - Grand Traverse Region (Box 79)
    - Great Britain (Box 79)
    - Great Falls, Montana (Box 79)
    - Greenville (Box 79)
    - Greenville, Ohio (Box 79)
    - Grosse Pointe (Box 79)
    - Guatemala (Box 79)
    - Hammond, Indiana (Box 79)
    - Hampton Roads, Virginia (Box 79)
    - Harrisburg, Pennsylvania (Box 79)
    - Hartford, Connecticut (Box 80)
    - Hastings (Box 80)
    - Hazelton, Pennsylvania (Box 80)
    - Hillsdale (Box 80)
    - Holland (Box 80)
    - Hong Kong, China (Box 80)
    - Honolulu, Hawaii (Box 80)
    - Houghton and Hancock (Box 80)
    - Houston, Texas (Box 80)
    - Howell (Box 80)
    - Huntington, West Virginia (Box 80)
    - Huron County (Box 80)
    - Indianapolis, Indiana (Box 80)
    - Indian River, Florida (Box 80)
    - Ionia (Box 81)
    - Iosco County (Box 81)
    - Iowa City, Iowa (Box 81)
    - Iron County (Box 81)
    - Iron Mountain (Box 81)
    - Ironwood (Box 81)
    - Ithaca, New York (Box 81)
    - Jackson (Box 81)
    - Jacksonville, Florida (Box 81)
    - Jamestown, New York (Box 81)
    - Japan (Box 81)
    - Johnstown, Pennsylvania (Box 81)
    - Joliet, Illinois (Box 81)
    - Kalamazoo (Box 81)
    - Kansas City, Missouri (Box 81)
    - Kansas City, Missouri (Box 82)
    - Knoxville, Tennessee (Box 82)
    - Korea (Box 82)
    - Lafayette, Indiana (Box 82)
    - Lancaster, Pennsylvania (Box 82)
    - Lansing (Box 82)
    - Lapeer (Box 82)
    - LaPorte, Indiana (Box 82)
    - Lima, Ohio (Box 82)
      (see box 134 in Photographs: Class Reunions series and box 96 in Alumni Club Files)
    - Lincoln, Nebraska (Box 82)
    - Lincoln Park (Box 82)
    - Little Rock, Arkansas (Box 82)
    - Livonia (Box 82)
    - Long Beach, California (Box 82)
    - Long Island, New York (Box 82)
    - Lorain County, Ohio (Box 82)
    - Los Angeles (Box 83)
    - Louisville, Kentucky (Box 83)
    - Ludington (Box 83)
    - Madison, Wisconsin (Box 83)
    - Maine (Box 83)
    - Manila (Philippines) (Box 83)
    - Manistee (Box 83)
    - Manistique (Box 83)
    - Mansfield, Ohio (Box 84)
    - Marquette (Box 84)
    - Memphis, Tennessee (Box 84)
    - Menominee (Box 84)
    - Mexico (Box 84)
    - Miami, Florida (Box 84)
    - Mid-Hudson, New York (Box 84)
    - Midland (Box 84)
    - Milwaukee, Wisconsin (Box 85)
    - Minneapolis, Minnesota (Box 85)
    - Missoula, Montana (Box 85)
    - Monroe (Box 85)
    - Monterey Peninsula, California (Box 85)
    - Monticello, Illinois (Box 85)
    - Montreal, Canada (Box 85)
    - Morgantown, West Virginia (Box 85)
    - Mt. Clemens (Box 85)
    - Mt. Pleasant (Box 85)
    - Muncie, Indiana (Box 85)
    - Munising (Box 85)
    - Muskegon (Box 85)
  - E-M (Pt. 2)
    - Eugene, Oregon (Box 168)
    - Fort Lauderdale, Florida (Box 168)
    - Greater Boston (Box 168)
    - Lansing (Box 168)
    - Los Angeles (Box 168)
  - N-Z (Pt. 1)
    - Nanking, China (Box 86)
    - Nashville, Tennessee (Box 86)
    - Newberry (Box 86)
    - New Brunswick, New Jersey (Box 86)
    - New Guinea (Box 86)
    - New Hampshire (Box 86)
    - New Haven, Connecticut (Box 86)
    - New Orleans, Louisiana (Box 86)
    - New York, New York (Box 86)
    - New York, New York (Box 87)
      (see also Andrews correspondence in box 134 in Photographs: Class Reunions series)
    - Niagara Falls, New York (Box 87)
    - Nicaragua (Box 87)
      (see box 134 in Photographs: Class Reunions series)
    - Niles (Box 87)
    - Norfolk, Virginia (Box 87)
    - Norman, Oklahoma (Box 87)
    - North Dakota (Box 88)
    - Northeastern Pennsylvania (Box 88)
    - Northeastern Wisconsin (Box 88)
    - Northern New Jersey (Box 88)
    - North Shore (Chicago), Illinois (Box 88)
    - Northville (Box 88)
    - Oak Ridge, Tennessee (Box 88)
    - Oklahoma City, Oklahoma (Box 88)
    - Olympia, Washington (Box 88)
    - Omaha, Nebraska (Box 88)
    - Otsego (Box 88)
    - Owosso (Box 88)
    - Palm Beach, Florida (Box 88)
    - Paris, France (Box 88)
    - Pasadena, California (Box 88)
    - Peking, China (Box 88)
    - Peoria, Illinois (Box 88)
    - Peru (Box 88)
    - Petoskey (Box 88)
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 88)
    - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania (Box 89)
    - Phoenix, Arizona (Box 89)
    - Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania (Box 89)
    - Pittsfield, Massachusetts (Box 89)
    - Plymouth (Box 89)
    - Pontiac (Box 90)
    - Port Huron (Box 90)
    - Portland, Maine (Box 90)
    - Portland, Oregon (Box 90)
    - Portsmouth, Ohio (Box 90)
    - Providence, Rhode Island (Box 90)
    - Puerto Rico (Box 90)
    - Quito, Ecuador (Box 90)
    - Reno, Nevada (Box 90)
    - Richmond, Indiana (Box 90)
    - Richmond, Virginia (Box 90)
    - Ridge Country, Florida (Box 90)
    - River Rouge (Box 90)
    - Rochester (Box 90)
    - Rochester, Minnesota (Box 90)
    - Rochester, New York (Box 91)
    - Rockford, Illinois (Box 91)
    - Romeo (Box 91)
    - Royal Oak (Box 91)
    - Saginaw (Box 91)
    - St. Clair (Box 91)
    - St. Clair Shores (Box 91)
    - St. Louis, Missouri (Box 91)
    - St. Petersburg, Florida (Box 92)
    - San Antonio, Texas (Box 92)
    - San Diego, California (Box 92)
    - Sandusky, Ohio (Box 92)
    - San Francisco, California (Box 92)
    - Sarasota, Florida (Box 92)
    - Sault Ste. Marie (Box 92)
    - Savannah, Georgia (Box 92)
    - Schenectady, New York (Box 92)
    - Shanghai, China (Box 93)
    - Seattle, Washington (Box 93)
    - Sioux City, Iowa (Box 93)
    - Sioux Falls, South Dakota (Box 93)
    - South Bend, Indiana (Box 93)
    - Southwestern Connecticut (Box 94)
    - Spokane, Washington (Box 94)
    - Springfield, Illinois (Box 94)
    - Springfield, Massachusetts (Box 94)
    - Springfield, Ohio (Box 94)
    - Stark County, Ohio (Box 94)
    - State College, Pennsylvania (Box 94)
    - Steubenville, Ohio (Box 94)
    - Sturgis (Box 94)
    - Suburban New Jersey (Box 94)
    - Syracuse, New York (Box 94)
    - Tacoma, Washington (Box 94)
    - Taipei, Taiwan (Box 94)
    - Tampa, Florida (Box 94)
    - Terre Haute, Indiana (Box 94)
    - Three Rivers (Box 94)
    - Toronto, Canada (Box 94)
    - Traverse City (Box 95)
    - Tri-Cities (Rock Island and Moline, Illinois and Davenport, Iowa) (Box 95)
    - Tucson, Arizona (Box 95)
    - Tulsa, Oklahoma (Box 95)
    - Turkey (Box 95)
    - Twin Cities (Minneapolis-St. Paul, Minnesota) (Box 95)
    - Uniontown, Pennsylvania (Box 95)
    - Utah (Salt Lake City) (Box 95)
    - Utica, New York (Box 95)
    - Venezuela (Box 95)
    - Vermont (Box 95)
    - Washington, D.C (Box 95)
    - Washington, D.C (Box 96)
    - Waterloo, Iowa (Box 96)
    - Lima, Ohio (also in box 134) (Box 96)
    - West Palm Beach, Florida (Box 96)
    - Wheeling, West Virginia (Box 96)
    - Whittier, California (Box 96)
    - Wichita, Kansas (Box 96)
    - Wilmington, Delaware (Box 96)
    - Worcester, Massachusetts (Box 96)
    - Wyandotte (Box 96)
    - York, Pennsylvania (Box 96)
    - Youngstown, Ohio (Box 96)
  - N-Z (Pt. 2)
    - New Hampshire (Box 168)
    - Palm Beach, Florida (Box 168)
    - Phoenix (Box 168)
    - Plymouth, Massachusetts (Box 168)
    - Raleigh (Box 168)
    - San Diego (Box 168)
    - Southern Fairfield County, Florida (Box 168)
    - Tallahassee (Box 168)
    - Tampa Bay (Box 168)
    - Washington, D.C. (Box 168)
- Alumni Societies, 1951-2001 (with gaps)
  Specific schools, colleges, or special interest groups comprise the Alumni Societies series (Boxes 155-156; and 168). Extensive documents on graduates of the dental hygienists program are contained here along with material on the schools and colleges of architecture, dentistry, education, library science, music, natural resources, nursing, pharmacy and public health. Specialized societies including basketball letter winners, Korean alumni, and the Michigan Black Law Alumni Society.
  To note are materials pertaining to the University of Michigan Black Alumni (UMBA), the African American Alumni Council (AAAC)-formerly the UMBA, and the Reunion of Black Graduates (RBG). This includes information about the Dr. Leonard F. Sain Award, the Dr. Martin Luther King, Jr. scholarship and symposium, the Camp Michigania retreat, and annual reunion for Black Graduates
  - University of Michigan Black Alumni (UMBA), 1976-2000 (with gaps)
    (Formerly the African American Alumni Council (AAAC).)
    - African American Alumni Council (AAAC), 1992-2001 (with gaps); undated
      (Also known as A3C.)
      - Administrative Files, 1992-2000
        - Correspondence, 1992-2000
          - 1992, 1999 (Box 168)
          - Affirmative Action, 1999-2000 (Box 168)
          - Diversity, 1991; 1993 (Box 168)
        - Directories and Membership Stats, 1994; 1998; undated (Box 168)
        - History and Bylaws, 1994-1998 (with gaps) (Box 168)
        - Minutes and Reports, 1994; 1998-1999 (Box 168)
        - Registration Committee, 1996 (Box 168)
      - Events, 1994-2001; undated
        - 20th Anniversary Gala, 1996 (Box 168)
        - Camp Michigania Retreat, 1998-2001
          - Correspondence, 1999-2001 (Box 168)
          - Financial Files, 1999-2000; undated (Box 168)
          - Mailing Lists and Rosters, 1999-2000 (Box 168)
          - Miscellaneous, 1998-2001 (Box 168)
          - Registration Forms, 1999-2000 (Box 168)
          - Surveys, undated (Box 168)
        - Other Events, 1994-2001 (with gaps) (Box 168)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr., 1986-2001 (with gaps); undated
        - Martin Luther King, Jr. Scholarship, 1986-1993 (Box 159)
        - MLK, Jr. Scholarship Committee, 1990-2001 (with gaps); undated (Box 168)
        - MLK, Jr. Symposium Committee, 1994-1995; undated (Box 168)
    - Black Alumni Leadership Groups, 1987 (Box 168)
    - Directories, 1994; undated
      - 1994, 2000; undated (Box 168)
      - undated (Box 168)
    - Dr. Leonard F. Sain Award, 1999; 2001 (Box 168)
    - Events and Programs, 1993; 1996-1997 (Box 168)
    - Reunion of Black Graduates (RBG), 1977-2000 (with gaps); undated
      - Administrative Files, 1984-2000 (with gaps)
        - Committee Meetings, 1984-2000
          - Past Reunion Chairs Committee Meetings, 1990-1994; undated (Box 168)
          - Registration Sub-Committee Final Report and Registration Lists, 1992-1994 (with gaps) (Box 168)
          - Reunion of Black Graduates Committee Meetings, 1977-2000 (with gaps) (Box 168)
          - Souvenir Book Club Sub-Committee meetings, 1985-1992 (with gaps) (Box 168)
          - Strategic Planning Committee meetings, 1992-1998 (with gaps) (Box 168)
        - Correspondence, 1989-1998 (with gaps) (Box 168)